pixelunion.net 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Website users and product purchasers - Pixel Union

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit our website (www.pixelunion.net) or purchase or install one of our products. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions.

#### How we collect information

##### Website

When you visit our website, we collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the site, we collect information about the pages or products viewed, which websites or search terms referred you to the site, and information about how you interact with the site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, including how to disable them, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the site, and collect data such as your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the site.
  * Google Analytics is used to track how you arrived on the site and how you might be spending your time while on the site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through our website, we collect certain information, including your name, billing address, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” Any payment information you enter, including credit card numbers and PayPal account information, is NOT stored on our site but directed to a third-party system (Stripe or PayPal).

When we refer to “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking about both Device Information and Order Information.

#### Apps

We collect certain Personal Information when you install the following apps:

##### Pixelpop, Free Shipping & Discount Bar, Countdown Sales Timer

We collect your store URL, along with your name, email, address, timezone, and location. We also collect any email addresses your customers enter via the app. This allows us to provide the features and functionality of the app, such as scheduled events (popups, sales and promotion banners, timers, etc.), location-based events, and any email integration you’ve enabled.

##### Wholesale Club

We collect your Shopify store URL, along with your name, telephone number, address, timezone, location. This allows us to create draft orders for your store based on pricing feature(s) you’ve enabled.

Once you’ve uninstalled one of our apps, we may store your data for up to 60 days in order to reach out to gather customer experience and usage feedback, and/or to contact you with promotional and win-back campaigns for a limited period.

#### Third-Party Marketplaces

When you purchase one of our products through a third-party marketplace such as Shopify or BigCommerce, we collect your store name and shop domain, along with your email address. We use this information to communicate with you and provide customer support when you contact us.

#### How we use information

We use the Order Information we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the site, including processing your payment information and providing you with invoices and order confirmations. Additionally, we use this Order Information to communicate with you; screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and, when in line with the preferences you’ve shared with us, provide you with information or promotional offers relating to our products and services.

We use the Device Information we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address) and more generally to improve and optimize our site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

#### How we share information

We share your Personal Information with the following third parties to help us conduct our business and support our customers as described above.

We use Stripe to process payments in our online store. You can read more about how Stripe uses your Personal Information at [stripe.com/ca/privacy](http://stripe.com/ca/privacy).

We use PayPal as an alternative way of processing payments in our online store. You can read more about how PayPal uses your Personal Information at [paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](http://paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use our website. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information at [google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can also opt-out of Google Analytics at [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use MailChimp and Drip for email marketing and to maintain our customer lists. You can read more about how MailChimp and Drip use your Personal Information at [mailchimp.com/legal/privacy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) and [drip.com/privacy](https://www.drip.com/privacy).

We use Intercom and HelpScout to communicate with you and provide customer support when you contact us. You can read more about how Intercom and HelpScout use your Personal Information at [intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy) and [helpscout.net/company/legal/privacy](https://www.helpscout.net/company/legal/privacy/).

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

As described above, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe could be of interest to you. For more information on how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of Facebook and Google targeted advertising at [facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads) and [google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous).

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

#### "Do not track"

Please note that we do not alter our site’s data collection and use practices when we see a “Do Not Track” signal from your browser.

#### Protecting your rights

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access any personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us via one of the methods described below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident, we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example, if you make an order through the site) or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the U.S.

#### Data retention

When you place an order through our site, we maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. Customer information will be retained in our system for a period of three years or as long as you’re an active user of our products.

#### Changes to this policy

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons.

#### Contact us

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at [info@pixelunion.net](mailto:info@pixelunion.net) or by mail at 202-1221 Broad Street, Victoria, BC, V8W 1V7, Canada.
